Frasier mss., 1934-2014 LMC 2962
Lilly Library
- Show Business Homicides
  - Bennison, Louis - sheet music feat. Margaret Lawrence (Ovflat 34)
  - Benson, Lyric (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Berg, Alan (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Bern, Paul (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Bern, Paul - photo (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Bhatt, Urmila (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Big L (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Big Lurch (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Big Stretch (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Blackburn, Ronald (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Blake, Robert, 2 Folders (Box 11, Folder 13-14)
  - Boham, Timothy J. (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Bornais, Claude (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Bourn, Verlon (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Brancato, Lillo (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Brando, Christian (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Brathwaite, Junior (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Buckland, Wilfred (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Bugz (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Burmeister, Christoffer (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Byard, Jaki (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - C-Murder (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Cabot-Roman, Susan (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Camoflauge (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Campbell, Margaret (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Cantat, Bertrand (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Caux, Claude (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - CAVLAR (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Chediak, Almir (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Childs, Evelyn (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Clarke, Rowan (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Clary, Wilton (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Cleaves, Robert Weldon (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Codona, Alfredo (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Colby, Barbara (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Colwell, Timothy (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Cooke, Sam, 2 Folders (Box 11, Folder 40-41)
  - Cooley, Spade (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Cortez, Angel (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Crane, Bob (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Crane, Cheryl, 2 Folders (Box 11, Folder 45-46)
  - Crittenden, T. D. (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Cunnane, Barry (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Cupit, Jennifer (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Da Prato, Emilia (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Davidson, Quentin (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Davis, Eric De Sean (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Davis, Myra (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Del Mar, Claire (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Diehl, Mary Louise (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Dismukes, George (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Dolla (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Door, William H. (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Dorsey, Leslie (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Duarte, Pablo (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Dube, Lucky (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Dunne, Dominique (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Echevarria, Lydia (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Engels, Virginia (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Etheridge, La Jean (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Europe, Jim (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Evans, Mal (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Forrester, Rhett (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Forsberg, Florence (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Foth, Steve (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Frachet, eric (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Fragson, Harry (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Fragson, Harry - photo postcard (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Franklin, Melvin B. (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Freaky Tah (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Frodl, Hehmut (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Fula, Yafeu (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Fuller, Bobby (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Gaye, Marvin (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Gentry, James B. (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Gelman, Eric (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Glahn, Rebecca (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Gobert, Dedrick (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Gomez, Audrey (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Gonzalez, Israel Chapa (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Gordon, Jim (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Goya, Tito (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Gray, King (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Gunter, Cornell (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Harger, Burt (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Harrison, Danny (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Hartman, Brynn (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Harvey, Bryan (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Harvey, Gerald (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Hassan, Muzzamil (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Haskell, Presley (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Hedderel, Rivet (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Hill, Alan (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Hinkley, Ineka Margaret (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - Holmes, John (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - Horner, Mark (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - Howard, Malcolm (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - Howden, Victoria (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - Huffman, David Oliver (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - Hull, Jay (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - Icewood, Blade (Box 12, Folder 60)
  - Ince, Thomas H. (Box 12, Folder 61)
  - Isenberg, Caroline (Box 12, Folder 62)
  - Ivers, Peter (Box 12, Folder 63)
  - Jackson, Al (Box 12, Folder 64)
  - Jackson, Michael (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Jam Master Jay (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Januskevicius, Melissa A. (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Jenkins, Ryan Alexander (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Jerome, Helene (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Johnson, Robert (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Jones, Kenneth Bruce (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Jung, Paul (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Kallman, Richard (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Kanyva (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Kean, Norman (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Kelly, George Augustus (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Kelly, Paul (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Kelly, Paul - photograph (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Kilian, Victor (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Kilian, Victor - photograph (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - King, Natel (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Knight, Terry (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Knox, Robert Arthur (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Kupcinet, Karyn (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - La Rock, Scott (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Landau, Jack (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Laney, Barbara Jean (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Lawes, Henry (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Lee, Anthony (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Lennon, John, 2 Folders (Box 13, Folder 26-27)
  - Leonard, Harry (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Lees, Robert (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Leopold, Joseph (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Longet, Claudine (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Loucks, David (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Mac Dre (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Mac the Camoflage Assassin (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - McCall, Roger (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - McMullen, Tara Correa (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - McNeelley, Robert E. (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Madingoane, Tebogo (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Mansfield, Edward (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Maloney, Robert N. (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Meek, Joe (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Melrose, Percy C. (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Menson, Michael (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Merker, Jack Ronald (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Mihalea, Ioan Luchian (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Miller, Lyndl (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Miller, Seagram (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Milosevic, Milos (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - Mineo, Sal (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Mineo, Sal - photograph (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Minor, Charlie (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Mr. Lee (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Mr. Livewire (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Mitchell Brothers (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Monday, Jerry (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Monroe, Marilyn, 2 Folders (Box 14, Folder 8-9)
  - Morelle, Denise (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Morgan, Lee (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Moss, Al (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Munro, Viola G. (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Myles, Raymond A. (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Nance, Jack (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Narcocorrido (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Narcocorrido - Sanchez, Chalino (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Narcocorrido - Gomez, Sergio (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Neal, Jackie (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Neal, Tom (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Neal, Tom - photograph (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Newt, Ronnie (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Ngor, Haing (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Niquette, Richard (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Nixon-Nirdlinger, Fred G. (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Norwood, John (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Notorious B.I.G. (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Novarro, Ramon (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Novarro, Ramon - photographs (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Olsson, Tony (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Omer, Danielle (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Ott, Paul Alan (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Palmer, Pearl (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Panou, Akis (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Pappalardi, Felix (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Parks, Wole (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Parnell, Wallace R. (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Parsa, Nasrat (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Pasolini, Pier Paolo (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Pastorius, Jaco (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Peaklica, Piseth (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Perez, Daniela (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Poulain, Jean-Paul (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - Priceless Game (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Pringle, Kevin (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Pringle, Val (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Professor Backwards (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Proof (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Radin, Roy (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Ramirez, Israel (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Raver, Harry (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Reeves, George (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Reid-Thomas, Elliott (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Reilly, Catherine (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Renaudin, Lester (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Ritchie, Adele (Box 15, Folder 13)
    Includes 1911 postcard of Ritchie
  - Robertson, William T. (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Rogers, Derek (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Rose, George (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Rosolino, Frank (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Ross, Arthur (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Ross, Nat (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Rothenberg, Paul (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Rountree, Roderick "Khalil" (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Rovig, Melita Powell (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Rudebeck, John W. (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - St. Louis, Keith (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Salmi, Albert (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Salanti, Theodore (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Sampih (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Sampson, John E. (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Sanders, Scott (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Santana, Merlin (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Schaeffer, Rebecca (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Schuster, Roy (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Schwartzbauer, Jessica (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Scott, Linda (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Scott, Walter (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Selena (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Shabalala, Headman (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Shakur, Tupac (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Shibley, Nassib (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - da Silva, Ramos (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Simmons, Kadamba (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Simpson, O. J. (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Simpson, O. J. - National Enquirers (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Smith, Allen (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Smith, Jay R. (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Smith, Robert McAdam (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Sorrells, Robert (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Soulja Slim (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Spector, Phil (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Stahl, Jennifer (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - Stiles, Grady F. Jr. (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - Stohn, Carl (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - Stratten, Dorothy (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - Stromberg, Larry (Box 15, Folder 54)
  - Struebing, Kurt Alan (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Talkov, Igor (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Tamim, Suzanne (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Tanin, Ihor (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Tate, Sharon (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Taylor, William Desmond (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Taylor, William Desmond - photograph of Mary Miles Minter (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Thomas, Kid (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Tillis, Sanford (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Todd, Thelma (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Todd, Thelma - photograph (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Torres, Angelo (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Tosh, Peter (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Troutman, Larry (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Van Alstyne, Harold (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Van der Walt, Deon (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Van Gogh, Theo (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Van Pallandt, Frederik (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Velez, Lilian (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Velez, Lilian - sheet music (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Vicious, Sid (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Wagenheim, Charles (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Wagenheim, Charles - photograph (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Walker, Kenneth (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Walters, Homer M. (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Warner, Jewel (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Wizzart, Keisha (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Wolf, Steve (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Wyatt, Nan (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Wassel, Jawed (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Williams, Jermaine (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Wilson, Nathaniel (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Yasuda, Yoshiki (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Yella (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Young, Gig (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Young, Gig - photograph (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Zapata, Mia (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Zazueta, Zachary (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Lists of potential entries, 2 Folders (Box 16, Folder 39-40)
  - Magazines with lists of potential entries (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - "New cases" (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - "Death Metal" (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - "Athletes" (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Hollywood maps/guides (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Corrected proofs (folders 1-2), 2010; 2 Folders (Box 16, Folder 46-47)
  - Corrected proofs (folder 3), 2010 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Typescript draft, 2 Folders (Box 17, Folder 2-3)
  - Unused entries
    - Unused research (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - List of homicides to not include (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Baker, Lee (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Beckford, Theophilus (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Blanca, Nida (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Boggs, Frank (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Cannon, D. O. (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Christi, Frank (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Cosby, Ennis (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Curtis, King (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Deleon, Skylar J. (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Dowell, Philip (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - DuFresne, Nicole (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Duggal, Mukesh (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Ellis, Jimmy (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Evans, Barry (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - George, Barry (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Gottschalk, Robert E. (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Hasni, Cheb (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Kaufmann, Gunther (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Kumar, Gulshan (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Matoub, Lounes (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - McCaskie, Sonja (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Parker, Jeffrey (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Parsons, Sonny (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Rajvansh, Priya (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Sinclair, Robert (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Talbot, Tyson (Box 17, Folder 31)
- Kenneth Anger
  - Correspondence, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence, 1992; 2 Folders (Box 17, Folder 40-41)
  - Correspondence, 1993; 2 Folders (Box 18, Folder 1-2)
  - Correspondence, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 2003; 3 Folders (Box 18, Folder 12-14)
  - Correspondence, 2004; 4 Folders (Box 18, Folder 15-18)
  - Correspondence, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, 2006; 2 Folders (Box 18, Folder 20-21)
  - Correspondence, 2007 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, 2008; 3 Folders (Box 19, Folder 23-25)
  - Correspondence, 2009; 8 Folders (Box 19, Folder 26-33)
  - Correspondence (oversize), 2009 (Ovflat 34)
  - Correspondence (folders 1-4), 2010; 4 Folders (Box 19, Folder 34-37)
  - Correspondence (folders 5-8), 2010; 4 Folders (Box 20, Folder 1-4)
  - Correspondence, 2011; 3 Folders (Box 20, Folder 5-7)
  - Correspondence, 2012; 3 Folders (Box 20, Folder 8-10)
  - Correspondence, 2013; 3 Folders (Box 20, Folder 11-13)
  - Correspondence, 2014 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, undated (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Icons by Kenneth Anger (Box 20, Folder 16)
    Work about Anger's oeuvre with writings by Anger, inscribed to Frasier
  - Foreword and materials for Suicide in the Entertainment Industry (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Materials and correspondence regarding Show Business Homicides (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence between Lee Harris and Frasier (Box 20, Folder 19)
    Harris was a friend of Anger's
  - Photographs - Alcatraz (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Photographs of Anger (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Photographs - San Francisco Freedom Day Parade, 1992? (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Michael Jackson memorial clippings, publications, and ephemera, 2009; 5 Folders (Box 21, Folder 2-6)
  - Michael Jackson memorial clippings, publications, and ephemera, 2009 (Ovflat 34)
  - Michael Jackson - memorial VHS (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous, 1934-1971 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Commemorative lighters (Box 22)